indiegamestand.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy - IndieGameStand

**Effective Date: July 25th, 2012**

Your privacy is important, so IndieGameStand ("IndieGameStand," “The Company,” "we," "us," or "our") has created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the Service, why we collect it and how it is used. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of the Service; it does not apply to other online or offline Company sites, products or services. The terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to the customer/purchaser utilizing our Service. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use. By using the Service, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy that we will include on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use.

**What Information Is Collected?**  
"Personally Identifiable Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home. IndieGameStand collects the following Personally Identifiable Information from you when you use our Service: your email address, and payment information (credit card and address, PayPal, or Amazon information). If you correspond with us by email or through the Service, we may retain the content of your messages, your email address and our responses.

IndieGameStand also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features.

**How Is Such Information Used?**  
We use the data that you provide or we collect to provide you the services offered on our Service. The Company uses your email address to create an account and organize your game download page and to notify you of future promotions if you sign-up for our newsletter.

IndieGameStand uses the data you enter on the Service, such as the price you enter, to make sure that your contributions go to the right places. We also may use the site data collected to produce general and anonymous statistics about consumer behavior.

We may use certain information about you internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

**Is The Information Shared or Disclosed?**  
IndieGameStand does not sell or share the information it collects hereunder except as described in this Privacy Policy. Information collected from you is disclosed and used to complete and support your purchases from and use of our Service and to comply with any requirements of law. For example, we may disclose information to third party payment processors. We may also disclose information to third party social networks at your direction, e.g. when you "tweet" or "like" something on the Service.

From time to time, we may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Service together with a third party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events.

IndieGameStand may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on IndieGameStand or the Service; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of IndieGameStand; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of IndieGameStand, its web sites or the public. If IndieGameStand or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that IndieGameStand goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of IndieGameStand may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Account Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We DO NOT store any financial information, credit card, or account numbers. All financial transactions are protected and processed by the payment providers that we utilize for our service. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to IndieGameStand or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

**International Transfers**  
Personal information collected on the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which the Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Cookies**  
Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files "cookies" that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired.

**Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. We encourage parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online.

**Choice**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into and editing your profile. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  You can contact us if you would like your account closed. Once we have verified your identity, we can remove all your personal details and IP on request.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**  
By using this Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Privacy Policy provision. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on this Service which it is your responsibility to review. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

**Contacting IndieGameStand**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Company, please contact us by emailing info@indiegamestand.com.
